欢迎来到《基于LangChain的大语言模型应用开发》的短期课程。
Welcome to this short course on LangChain for large language model application development.
通过对大语言模型使用提示（Prompt），现在可以比以往任何时候都更快地开发AI应用程序。
By prompting an LLM or large language model, it is now possible to develop AI applications much faster than ever before.
但是一个应用程序可能需要多次对大语言模型写提示并对它输出的结果进行解析。
But an application can require prompting an LLM multiple times and parsing its output.
因此，需要编写很多胶水代码。
And so there's a lot of glue code that needs to be written.
Harrison Chase创建的LangChain使这个开发过程变得更容易。
LangChain created by Harrison Chase makes this development process much easier.
我很高兴邀请到Harrison，他与deeplearning.ai合作创建了这个短期课程，教大家如何使用这个神奇的工具。
I'm thrilled to have Harrison here, who had built this short course in collaboration with deeplearning.ai to teach how to use this amazing tool.
谢谢Andrew的邀请，我很高兴来到这里。
Thanks for having me. I'm really excited to be here.
LangChain起初是一个用于构建大语言模型应用的开源框架。
LangChain started as an open source framework for building LLM applications.
当时有些人在开发LLM的复杂应用，当我与他们交流时，发现了可以从中有一些公共的抽象，于是LangChain应运而生。
It came about when I was talking to a bunch of folks in the field who were building more complex applications and saw some common abstractions in terms of how they were being developed.
迄今为止，LangChain在社区中的采用情况非常令人激动。
And we've been really thrilled at the community adoption of LangChain so far.
期待与大家分享，也期待看到大家用它做出精彩的作品。
And so look forward to sharing it with everyone here and look forward to seeing what people build with it.
事实上，从一个现象你就可以看到LangChain的良好发展势头：它不仅拥有众多用户，还有数百名贡献者为其开源项目做出了贡献。
And in fact, as a sign of LangChain's momentum, not only does it have numerous users, but there are also many hundreds of contributors to the open source.
这对于它的快速发展至关重要。
And this has been instrumental for its rapid rate of development.
这个团队更新代码和迭代功能的速度令人惊叹。
This team really ships code and features at an amazing pace.
希望在学习完这个短期课程后，你也能迅速用LangChain搭建出很酷的应用。
So hopefully, after this short course, you'll be able to quickly put together some really cool applications using LangChain.
说不定你还能一起参与贡献LangChain开源项目。
And who knows, maybe you even decide to contribute back to the open source LangChain effort.
LangChain是一个用于构建LLM应用的开源开发框架。
LangChain is an open source development framework for building LLM applications.
我们有两个不同的包，一个是Python，另一个是JavaScript（TypeScript）。
We have two different packages, a Python one and a JavaScript(TypeScript) one.
LangChain注重组合和模块化。
They're focused on composition and modularity.
LangChain一个很有价值的地方是有很多可以单独使用或与其他组件结合使用的独立组件。
So they have a lot of individual components that can be used in conjunction with each other or by themselves. And so that's one of the key value adds.
另一个有价值的地方是有许多不同的用例，
And then the other key value add is a bunch of different use cases.
可以将这些模块化组件链式组合成更完整的应用程序，并且非常容易上手。
So chains of ways of combining these modular components into more end-to-end applications and making it very easy to get started with those use cases.
在这个课程中，我们将介绍LangChain的常见组件。
In this class, we'll cover the common components of LangChain.
我们会讨论模型。
So we'll talk about models.
我们会讨论提示，这是让模型做有用和有趣事情的方法。
We'll talk about prompts, which are how you get models to do useful and interesting things.
我们会讨论索引，也就是检索召回数据，并且将数据与模型结合起来。
We'll talk about indexes, which are ways of ingesting data so that you can combine it with models.
然后我们会讨论链式应用，更多端到端的用例以及代理，
And then we'll talk about chains, which are more end-to-end use cases along with agents,
代理一种非常令人兴奋的端到端用例，使用大语言模型作为推理引擎。
which are a very exciting type of end-to-end use case, which uses the model as a reasoning engine.
我们也感谢Ankush Gola，
We're also grateful to Ankush Gola,
他与Harrison Chase共同创立了LangChain，
who is the co-founder of LangChain alongside Harrison Chase,
他在这些材料的思考和短课程的创建中也做出了很大的贡献。
for also putting a lot of thoughts into these materials and helping with the creation of this short course.
在深度学习和AI方面，Geoff Ladwig、Eddie Shyu和Diala Ezzedine也为这些材料做出了贡献。
And on the deep learning, the AI side, Geoff Ladwig, Eddie Shyu, and Diala Ezzedine have also contributed to these materials.
那么，让我们继续下一个视频，了解LangChain的：模型、提示和解析器。
And so with that, let's go on to the next video where we'll learn about LangChain's: Models, Prompts, and Parsers.